<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shiloh Williams</title>
    <link>https://isawil.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shiloh Williams</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="https://isawil.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://isawil.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isawil.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Shiloh Williams and I use they/them pronouns. I currently work as the Acting Head of the Digital Scholarship Lab and the Map, Data &amp;amp; GIS Library at Brock University, where I provide instructional and research support for data science on campus. Prior to that, I was the Data Visualization and GIS Librarian at the University of Texas at Arlington. I have also worked at the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) and the Center for the Study of Political Graphics, where I analyzed and visualized collections data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://isawil.github.io/resume/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isawil.github.io/resume/cv/</guid>
      <description>Hello </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://isawil.github.io/portfolio/data-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isawil.github.io/portfolio/data-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>While working at academic institutions I have had the opportunity to work on various data science projects, including the following, some of which is discussed in my blog.
COVID-19 dashboard In collaboration with Peace Ossom Williamson, I created a Tableau dashboard that reported COVID-19 case counts in the Dallas-Fort Worth Metroplex. The insights gained from the process informed an analysis of public health data availability that I co-authored and which was peer-reviewed and published in JMIR Public Health and Surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://isawil.github.io/resume/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://isawil.github.io/resume/resume/</guid>
      <description>Employment Acting Head, Digital Scholarship Lab / Map, Data &amp;amp; GIS Library Brock University, St. Catharines, Ontario, Canada January 2022 to Present
GIS and Data Services Librarian Brock University, St. Catharines, Ontario, Canada June 2021 to Present
Data Visualization and GIS Librarian University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, Texas, United States July 2019 to May 2021
Graduate Assistant University of California, Los Angeles April 2017 to June 2019
Graduate Intern Center for the Study of Political Graphics</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
